Guide to the Francis B. (Francis Butler) Loomis Papers: microfilm, 1897-1939
Department of Special Collections
- Descendants of Joseph Loomis in America and His Antecedents in the Old World, Series 8; 1 microfilm reel
Churchill, James S. Roll IV Book 4
Clark, Arthur A. Roll IV Book 4
Clark, Champ Roll V Folder 23
Clark, G. W. Roll III Book 2
Clark, Howard Roll IV Book 4
Clarkson, John S. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Clay, Brutus J. Roll IV Book 4
Clayton, Powell Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Book 22, Folder 23
Clemens, William M. Roll IV Book 3
Clinedinst, [?] Roll IV Book 4
Cole, William H. Roll IV Book 3
Collier, William M. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Collins, Victor Roll IV Book 4
Colne, Charles Roll III Book 2
Colt, Richard C. Roll IV Book 3
Columbian Legation Roll III Book 2
Conant, Harry A. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Conger, Charlotte M. Roll IV Book 3
Congressional Record Roll V Folder 23
Conkling, Alfred R. Roll IV Book 3
Conolly, A. A. Roll III Book 2
Converse, George A. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5 Roll V Folder 23
Cook, A. B. Roll IV Book 3
Cook - Stoddard Company Roll IV Book 3
Coolidge, L. A. Roll IV Book 3
Coombs, Leslie Roll IV Book 4
Coop, Frank E. Roll IV Book 4
Corbin, Henry C. Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Folder 22
Corea, Luis F. Roll IV Book 4
Cortelyou, George B. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5
Coulter, A. E. Roll IV Book 3
Covert, John C. Roll III Book 2
Coweles, William Roll IV Book 4
Cox, Hanson C. Roll IV Book 4
Coxe, Henry C. Roll IV Book 3
Cragts' Sons Roll III Book 1
Cramp, Sanuel Roll III Book 1
Crane, Charles R. Roll III Book 1, Book 2
Crane, Leonard A. Roll III Book 1
Crawford, John Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 4
Creelman, James Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 4 Roll V Book 21, Folder 23
Creighton, David H. Roll IV Book 4
Critchfield, George W. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5 Roll V Folder 22
Crocker, William H. Roll III Book 2 Roll V Book 23, Folder 24
Cromwell, William N. Roll III Book 1
Cropper, William H. Roll V Folder 24
Crouse, H. P. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3
Crowell, John F. Roll IV Book 3
Crowley, Richard Roll IV Book 3
Culborson, Charles A. Roll III Book 2
Cullom, Shelby M. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Cummers, Samuel R. Roll IV Book 3
Cuneo, Sherman Roll IV Book 4
Cuppy, Hazlit A. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Curtis, L. B. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Curtis, William Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Folder 19
Cushing, Marshall Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5
Cutting, W. Bayard Roll IV Book 3
Dalong, Paul Roll III Book 2
Dalzell, John Roll III Book 2 Roll V Folder 22
Daneri, A. C. Roll IV Book 3
Daneri Brothers Roll IV Book 4
Daniel, John M. Roll IV Book 3
Daniel, Milton Roll III Book 2
Danziger, Adolph Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Dartford, O. H. Roll III Book 1
Dasent, Bury M. Roll IV Book 3
Dater, John G. Roll V Folder 19
Davenport, R. G. Roll III Book 2
Davidson, Charles M. Roll IV Book 3
Davidson, Harry P. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Davies, Ralph K. Roll V Book 24, Folder 25
Davis, Henry G. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Dawes, Charles Roll IV Book 4 Roll V Book 22, Folder 24
Dawes, Edwin Roll V Folder 19
Dawson, Thomas C. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Day, William Roll IV Book 3
d'Azevedo, J. C. Roll IV Book 4, Book 5
Deal, Henry B. Roll III Book 1
Dean, Charles R. Roll IV Book 4 Roll V Folder 22
Deitrich, James Roll IV Book 3
Delfino, Antonio E. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
De Long, Paul Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3
del Viso, Antonio Roll III Book 2
Denby, Edwin Roll V Folder 22
Deneen, Charles S. Roll IV Book 4
Dennison, E. Haldeman Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Deterding, Henry Roll V Folder 24
De Vault, Charles Roll V Book 24, Folder 25
Devol, Carroll Roll IV Book 3
Devol, Hattie Roll IV Book 4
Diaz, Porfirio Roll V Book 23, Folder 24
Dick, Charles Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5
Dickenson, Charles M. Roll IV Book 4
Diederich, Henry W. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Dietrich, Charles H. Roll IV Book 3
Dietrich, Herman R. Roll III Book 2
Dillingham, A. C. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4 Roll V Folder 21
Dockery, A. V. Roll IV Book 4
Dodge, H. Percival Roll IV Book 3
Dohrman, E. W. Roll V Folder 22
Dolge, Alfred Roll V Folder 25
Dolge, Rudolph Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5 Roll V Book 19, Book 21, Book 24, Folder 25
Dolliver, J. P. Roll III Book 1
Dos Passos, John R. Roll V Folder 23
Doty, William F. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Dove, J. Maury Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3
Dover, Elmer Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Dresser, Soloman R. Roll IV Book 4
Drew, John Roll V Folder 24
Dubois, James T. Roll III Book 1
Dudley, Irving Roll IV Book 4
Dudley, W. W. Roll III Book 2
Dunn, James R. Roll IV Book 4
Dunne, Frank V. Roll IV Book 4
Durand, H. Mortimer Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Duvall, Andrew Roll IV Book 4
Dyer, Rowland Roll IV Book 4
Edelman, Louis Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Edwards, Clarence R. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 4
Eells, William E. Roll IV Book 3
Egan, Thomas P. Roll IV Book 4
Elkins, Stephen B. Roll V Book 22, Folder 23
Elliot, A. B. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Elliot, C. D. Roll IV Book 4
Elliot, Charles W. Roll IV Book 3
Ellis, Wade H. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 4 Roll V Folder 19
Ellsworth, Luther T. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 4
Elmore, J. F. Roll IV Book 3
Ely, Robert E. Roll III Book 2
Embry, J. H. Roll III Book 1
Emerson, H. D. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 1
Emory, Frederick Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 4
Estournelles de Constant, Baron Roll V Folder 23
Euan-Smith, Charles Roll IV Book 4
Evans, H. Clay Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Evans, James F. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 4
Fairbanks, Charles W. Roll III Book 1
Fairbanks, J. E. Roll IV Book 4
Fassett, J. Sloat Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Fawcett, Walden Roll III Book 1
Fermin, A. Roll IV Book 4
Field, Charles K. Roll V Folder 24
Fieldwick, H. Roll V Folder 19
Figaro Roll V Folder 19
Fillmore, Charles W. Roll III Book 1
Financial Times Roll V Folder 24
Fish, Stuyvesant Roll IV Book 4
Fishback, George W. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Fiske, George M. Roll III Book 1
Flynn, E. F. Roll III Book 1
Flynn, M. W. Roll IV Book 3
Follett, A. Dewey Roll IV Book 3
Foord, John Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3
Foraker, Joseph B. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5 Roll V Book 20, Book 21, Folder 22
Forbes, Edgar A. Roll IV Book 4
Fosburg, James Roll V Folder 21
Foster, Arthur Roll IV Book 3
Foster, John G. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Fox, William C. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Francis, Charles S. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 4
Francis, David R. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll V Folder 23
Franklin, P. A. S. Roll V Book 22, Folder 23
French Canal Company Roll V Folder 19
French Embassy Roll IV Book 3
Frey, G. H. Roll IV Book 3
Frye, William P. Roll IV Book 4
Fuller, Arthur G. Roll IV Book 3
Funk, C. S. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Funk and Wagnolls Company Roll IV Book 3
Funston, Frederick Roll III Book 1
Gaitree, W. B. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 5
Gallagher, J. A. Roll IV Book 4
Gallinger, Jacob H. Roll III Book 1
Gambn, F[r]ederico Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Ganetson, Joseph Roll III Book 2
Gard, Daniel Hosner Roll IV Book 4
Gardner, A. L. Roll III Book 1
Garfield, James A. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Garfield Safe Deposit Company Roll III Book 1
Gates, S. A. Roll IV Book 4
Gaulin, Alphonse Roll IV Book 4
German Embassy Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
German Press Association Roll V Folder 23
Gessner, F. B. Roll III Book 2
Gettys, A. L. Roll IV Book 3
Geyers, W. F. Roll III Book 1
Gibbons, Cardinal Roll V Folder 21
Gibson, E. J. Roll III Book 1
Gillespie, T. A. Roll IV Book 3
Gilliland, George Roll IV Book 3
Given, Walker Roll III Book 2
Glass, A. W. Roll IV Book 3
Gleaves, Albert Roll IV Book 4
Glenn, Theodore E. Roll III Book 1
Goddard, George F. Roll IV Book 4
Goddard, Nelson Roll III Book 1
Goff, Thomas T. Roll IV Book 3
Goldschmidt, Louis Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4 Roll V Book 19, Folder 21
Gomar, Jose D. Roll IV Book 4
Gomes Ferreira, Alfredo de M. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Gompers, Samuel Roll V Folder 21
Goodnow, John Roll III Book 2
Gore, James H. Roll IV Book 4
Gorham, George C. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Goss, Mary W. Roll III Book 2
Gowdy, John K. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Gram, Harvey B. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Granger, Walter L. Roll III Book 1
Grant, Joseph D. Roll V Folder 24
Great Bear Spring Company Roll IV Book 3
Greene, W. Maxwell Roll IV Book 3
Gregory, Catheryn C. Roll III Book 1
Gribescock, Emil Roll IV Book 4
Grieser, H. A. Roll IV Book 4
Griffiths, John L. Roll IV Book 4
Griscom, Lloyd C. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5
Griswold, Edith J. Roll IV Book 3
Groothoff, [?] Roll V Folder 24
Grosvenor, Gilbert H. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Gugenheim, I. M. Roll III Book 1
Gulf Oil Company Roll V Folder 25
Gummere, Samuel R. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Gunsaulus, Edwin N. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Hadcock, John Roll IV Book 3
Hadley, Elliot Roll V Folder 23
Hague Tribunal Roll V Folder 23
Hahn, H. H. Roll III Book 2
Hale, Edward Everett Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Hale, Eugene Roll IV Book 4
Hale, Harry C. Roll III Book 2
Hale, Ruben B. Roll V Folder 24
Halford, A. J. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3
Halstead, Murat Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Hamilton, Stanislaus H. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5
Hamm, Walter C. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5
Hanauer, Simon W. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Handy, William M. Roll V Folder 23
Hanna, Hugh R. Roll III Book 2
Hanna, Marcus A. Roll III Book 1 Roll V Folder 25
Hanna, Philip C. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 4
Hanna, Walter C. Roll III Book 1
Hannsman, Carl A. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Hansen, Theodore Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 4
Harding, Warren G. Roll V Folder 24
Hardy, Arthur S. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Hargete, Frank Roll IV Book 3
Harjes, John H. Roll IV Book 4
Harrison, Mrs. Benjamin Roll III Book 2
Harrison, Charles C. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Hart, Charles B. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 4
Harvey, George Roll V Folder 23
Hathaway, John Roll IV Book 3
Haven, Joseph E. Roll IV Book 4
Hawk, William L. Roll IV Book 3
Hay, John Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Book 19, Book 20, Book 22, Book 23, Folder 25
Hay, Mrs. John Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Hay--Herran Treaty Roll V Folder 19
Hayes, John H. Roll IV Book 5
Hearst, William R. Roll V Book 21, Book 23, Folder 24
Heatwok, Joel P. Roll III Book 1
Hege, S. B. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Heistand, H. O. S. Roll IV Book 4
Helmle, George B. Roll IV Book 4
Helper, Hinton Rowan Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Hemick, Rolland J. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Henderson, T. J. Roll V Folder 24
Hepburn, William P. Roll III Book 1
Hergert, Gustav L. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Hernndez, Jose M. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Herrick, Myron T. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Folder 19
Hicks, John Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Higgins, Frank W. Roll IV Book 4
Higley, Warren Roll IV Book 4
Hill, David J. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Book 19, Folder 24
Hill, Ebenezer Roll III Book 2
Hill, Robert J. Roll III Book 1
Hill, William C. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5
Hioki, Eki Roll IV Book 3
Hitchcock, Ethan A. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Folder 21
Hitt, Robert M. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
H. L. Boulton and Company Roll IV Book 4
Hobart, I. C. Roll IV Book 4, Book 5
Hobbs, John F. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Hochdrfer, Richard H. Roll III Book 1
Hodges and Stearns Roll IV Book 3
Hollander, Jacob H. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5
Holls, Frederick W. Roll III Book 1
Holman, Alfred Roll V Book 23, Folder 24
Holt, Hamilton Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 4
Hooker, James J. Roll III Book 2
Hooper, J. J. Roll V Folder 19
Hooper, Osman Roll III Book 1
Hoover, Herbert Roll V Folder 24
Hopley, Joseph W. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Hoppes, John J. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 4
Howard, George Roll III Book 2
Howe, Church Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Howland, E. C. Roll IV Book 4
Hoyt, Henry M. Roll IV Book 3
Hoyt, John B. Roll IV Book 3
Hubbell, George W. Roll III Book 1
Huerta, Victoriano Roll V Folder 23
Hughes, Charles E. Roll V Folder 24
Hughes, O. D. J. Roll IV Book 4
Hull, Cordell Roll V Folder 25
Humphrey, Alexander C. Roll V Folder 21
Humphreys, W. E. Roll III Book 2
Hunt, G. Roll III Book 1
Hunt, William H. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 4
Huntington, Sanuel Roll IV Book 4
Hurst, Carl B. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Hurst, John Roll IV Book 3
Hutchinson, Norman Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5 Roll V Book 19, Folder 22
Hutchinson, P. D. Roll IV Book 3
Ide, George E. Roll IV Book 5
Ide, Kittey Roll IV Book 5
Ide, W. H. Roll IV Book 5
Ingalls, M. E. Roll V Folder 19
International Institute of Measurement Units Roll V Folder 24
International and Universal Exhibition at Brussels 1919 Roll V Book 21, Book 22, Folder 23
Ireland, Fred Roll V Folder 22
Irish, John P. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Irish, Irwin Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Folder 19
Ishii, Kikujiro Roll V Folder 24
Isthmian Canal Company Roll III Book 2
Italian Embassy Roll IV Book 3
Ito, Prince Roll V Folder 21
Jackson, John B. Roll III Book 2
Jacobson, A. D. Roll IV Book 4, Book 5
James T. White and Company, Publishers Roll V Folder 24
Japan Finance Commission Roll V Folder 24
Japan Society of America Roll V Folder 24
Japanese Legation Roll III Book 2
Jaurett, A. F. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5 Roll V Folder 19
Jenks, J. W. Roll IV Book 4, Book 5
Jewell, Henry M. Roll IV Book 3
John Hancock Mutual Benefit Life Insurance Company Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 4
Johnson, E. B. Roll III Book 2
Johnson, Emory R. Roll IV Book 4
Johnson, Felix S. S. Roll IV Book 4
Johnson, Hiram Roll V Folder 23
Johnson, James Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Johnson, Mrs. Mary A. Roll III Book 2
Johnson, William F. Roll III Book 2
Johnson, Willis Fletcher Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Johnson, Wynne and Company Roll III Book 2
Johnston, James Jr. Roll IV Book 4 Roll V Folder 22
Johnston, W. H. Roll V Folder 22
Jones, John Paul Roll V Folder 23
Joubert, Emilio C. Roll III Book 2
J. P. Morgan and Company Roll V Folder 22
Jordan, W. H. Roll III Book 2
Jusserand, Jean Jules Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Kahn, Julius Roll III Book 1 Roll V Folder 24
Katsura, Taro Roll V Book 21, Folder 22
Kean, John Roll IV Book 3
Keen, E. L. Roll IV Book 4
Keene, Francis B. Roll IV Book 4
Keifer, J. Warren Roll IV Book 4 Roll V Folder 23
Kellogg, Frank B. Roll V Folder 24
Kellogg, James C. Roll III Book 2
Kelly, James H. Roll III Book 2
Kelly, Thomas H. Roll III Book 2
Kennedy, Crammond Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 4
Kennedy, George E. Roll V Folder 25
Kennedy, J. Russell Roll V Folder 22
Kenney, A. D. Roll III Book 1
Kenney, A. S. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 4
Kenyon, William S. Roll V Folder 24
Ker, S. P. Roll III Book 1
Kerens, Richard C. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Book 21, Book 22, Folder 23
Kerens, Mrs. Richard C. Roll IV Book 3
Kerens, Vincent Roll V Book 22, Folder 23
Khan, Isaac Roll III Book 2
Kincaid, Edgar B. Roll IV Book 4
Kinchant, Robert H. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 4
King, Landreth H. Roll III Book 2
Kingsbury, S. A. Roll IV Book 4 Roll V Folder 24
Kioke, [?] Roll V Folder 24
Knowles, Horace G. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Knox, Philander C. Roll V Book 22, Folder 23
Kohlsaat, Charles W. Roll IV Book 4
Komura, Jutaro Roll V Book 21, Folder 22
Kraft's Sons Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3
Krenztin, Julius A. Roll IV Book 4
Kurtz, C. F. Roll IV Book 5
Kurtz, C. L. Roll IV Book 4, Book 5
Lafean, Daniel F. Roll IV Book 3
LaLane, Frank D. Roll V Folder 22
Lampton, W. J. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 4
Landis, Charles B. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 4
Landon, Francis G. Roll IV Book 3
Lane, Franklin Roll V Folder 23
Langer, Joseph J. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 4
Langerman, James H. Roll III Book 2
Langley, S. P. Roll IV Book 4
Lardy, Charles L. E. Roll III Book 1
Larrinaga, Tulio Roll IV Book 4 Roll V Folder 23
LaRue, H. B. Roll IV Book 4
Lawler, K. K. Roll III Book 1
Lawrence, [?] Roll V Folder 21
Lay, Julius G. Roll IV Book 4
Ledoux, Urbain J. Roll III Book 1
Lee Hung Chang Roll V Folder 21
Lee, Joseph W. J. Roll IV Book 3
Leger, J. N. Roll IV Book 4, Book 5
Leimert, Walter Roll V Folder 24
Lemmon, George T. Roll IV Book 4
Leon, A. C. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Leonard, H. S. Roll IV Book 4
Lepage, G. L. Roll V Folder 19
Le Roy, James A. Roll IV Book 4
Lesner, Clarence L. Roll III Book 2
Le Temps of Paris Roll V Folder 19
Levi Strauss and Sons Roll IV Book 3
Lewis, N. G. Roll V Folder 21
Libby, William H. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5
Liberty National Bank Roll III Book 1, Book 2
Limantour, Jose-Yves Roll V Folder 23
Lindauer, W. Roll III Book 2
Lindaur, J. J. Roll IV Book 4
Lindsay, John D. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Linn, Walter L. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Lipscomb, A. A. Roll III Book 2
Lithgow, A. W. Roll III Book 2
Littman, Eno Roll III Book 1
Livingston, Thomas H. Roll III Book 2
Lloyd, W. Roll III Book 2
Lockwood, Edwin C. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Lodge, Henry Cabot Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5 Roll V Folder 21
Loeb, William Jr. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5 Roll V Book 21, Book 22, Folder 25
Long, Bryon R. Roll IV Book 3
Long, Chester I. Roll IV Book 3
Longworth, Alice R. Roll V Folder 24
Longworth, Nicholas Roll IV Book 3, Book 4 Roll V Folder 24
Loomis, Burdett Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Loomis, Charles Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 4 Roll V Folder 24
Loomis, Dwight Roll III Book 1 Roll V Folder 23
Loomis, Elizabeth Roll V Book 19, Book 22, Folder 23
Loomis Family Association Roll V Folder 23
Loomis, Florence Roll V Folder 23
Loomis, Francis B. Roll V Folder 19
Loomis, Francis B. (Jimp) Jr. Roll V Book 23, Folder 24
Loomis, F. Kent Roll III Book 1
Loomis, Harry E. Roll IV Book 4
Loomis, Jennie Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Lopez, Rafael S. Roll III Book 1
Lynch, Frank E. Roll IV Book 4
Lyon, Ernest Roll IV Book 4
McBride, James J. Roll III Book 2
McCabe, Alex S. Roll IV Book 3
McCabe, Charles C. Roll IV Book 3
McCain, George Nox Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 4
McCall, Henry Roll IV Book 4
McCalla, B. W. Roll IV Book 4
McCammon, Charles Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Folder 24
McCarthy, Thomas B. Roll IV Book 4
McCartney, J. H. Roll III Book 1
McCawley, Charles L. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
McClellan, George B. Roll IV Book 4
McClure, Samuel G. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3
McComas, Louis E. Roll III Book 1
McCook, John J. Roll IV Book 4
McCormick, E. O. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 4
McCormick, Robert S. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5 Roll V Folder 20
McCortney, J. H. Roll IV Book 5
McCullom, Shelby Roll IV Book 4
McDonald, Alex Roll IV Book 3
McGee, W. J. Roll IV Book 3
McGlynn, F. P. Roll III Book 1
McGuire, Mrs. Lillian Roll IV Book 3
McKee, Sidney S. Roll III Book 1
McKenney, F. D. Roll IV Book 4
Mackeys, [?] Roll IV Book 5
McKinley, William Roll V Book 22, Book 23, Folder 24
McLaurin, John C. Roll IV Book 4
McLeon, John R. Roll IV Book 4
McNally, James C. Roll IV Book 4
McNutt, Paul Roll V Folder 25
Maddox, Samuel Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Maddy, J. K. Roll IV Book 3
Magee, C. L. Roll IV Book 3
Magoon, Charles E. Roll IV Book 3
Magoon, Charles F. Roll IV Book 4
Mahany, Rowland B. Roll III Book 2
Malmross, Oscar Roll III Book 2
Maltus and Ware Roll III Book 2
Manheim, F. J. Roll V Folder 25
Manning, Wentworth Roll III Book 2
Marbury, Theodore Roll IV Book 4
Marcus and Company Roll III Book 2
Marcy, William L. Roll IV Book 3
Markley, Horace Roll IV Book 3
Marklirert, Leopold Roll IV Book 4
Marshall, Thomas R. Roll III Book 2 Roll V Folder 24
Martin, D. B. Roll V Folder 23
Martin, W. A. Roll III Book 1
Martin, William H. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Mason, Frank G. Roll III Book 2 Roll II Book 14
Mason, Frank H. Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Mast, Charles Roll V Folder 22
Mast, Cicero P. Roll III Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Mast, Clarence S. Roll IV Book 4
Mast, Foos and Company Roll IV Book 3
Mast, Joseph K. Roll III Book 1
Mast, P. P. Roll V Book 22, Folder 23
Matthews, R. G. Roll IV Book 3
Matthieu, J. C. Roll III Book 2
Maxwell, C. L. Roll III Book 2
May, DeCourcy Roll III Book 1
Mayers, Charles R. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4 Roll V Book 19, Folder 22
Mayor des Planches Eduardo Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 4
Mebbis, D. Ernest Roll III Book 1
The Medico-Legal Society Roll IV Book 5
Megata, Tanetaro Roll V Folder 24
Mellis, N. M. Roll IV Book 4, Book 5
Melliss, D. Ernest Roll III Book 2
Melliss, Norman T. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
Mellon, A. W. Roll V Folder 24
Melton, H. L. Roll III Book 2
Menelek II, Emperor of Abyssinia Roll V Book 19, Folder 24
Menkel, William Roll IV Book 3
Mercado, Lorenzo Roll IV Book 3, Book 5 Roll V Folder 19
Merou, M. Garcia Roll III Book 1
Merrill, Selah Roll IV Book 3
Merritt, R. F. R. Roll III Book 1
Messent, Josiah Roll IV Book 3
Metcalf, Victor H. Roll IV Book 4
Meyer, George V. L. Roll III Book 2
Michailis, L. F. Roll IV Book 4
Miles, H. E. Roll III Book 1
Miller, E. C. Roll IV Book 3
Miller, Leroy E. Roll III Book 1
Miller, M. W. Roll III Book 1
Millet, [?] Roll V Folder 21
Mitchell, James B. Roll IV Book 4
Mitchell, John Q. Roll III Book 1
Mitchelson, J. C. Roll IV Book 3
Moler, William Roll V Folder 23
Moncheur, Baron Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Book 22, Folder 23
Monroe Doctrine Roll V Folder 23
Montagna, G. C. Sr. Roll IV Book 3
Moody, William H. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4
Moore, John Bassett Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5 Roll V Book 19, Folder 25
Moore, Thomas Ewing Roll III Book 2
Morel, E. D. Roll IV Book 4
Morell, H. Roll III Book 1
Morgan, Douglas O. Roll IV Book 4
Morgan, J. Pierpoint Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Morgan, John T. Roll IV Book 3
Mohonk, Lake Roll V Folder 22
Moriya, R. N. Roll IV Book 3
Morris, Minor Roll III Book 2
Morris, Sidney S. Roll III Book 2
Morton, Henry E. Roll V Folder 21
Morton, Levi P. Roll III Book 1
Morton, Paul Roll IV Book 3, Book 4 Roll V Folder 21
Mueller, [?] Roll V Folder 19
Muoz, Jorge Roll IV Book 4
Munroe, Charles E. Roll III Book 2
Murray, C. B. Roll IV Book 4
Mutsu, Hirokitschi Roll III Book 2
National Academy of Political and Social Science Roll V Folder 23
Naval War College Roll V Folder 19
Neale, S. C. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5 Roll V Folder 23
Nelson, Knute Roll IV Book 3
Neuer, C. Roll IV Book 3
Nevins, Allan Roll V Folder 25
New, Harry S. Roll IV Book 5
Newberry, [?] Roll V Folder 22
Newcomb, William A. Roll V Folder 23
Newel, Stanford Roll IV Book 5
New York Herald Roll V Folder 19
New York Journal of Commerce Roll V Folder 22
New York Life Insurance Company Roll III Book 1, Book 2
New York Shipbuilding Company Roll III Book 1
The New York Sun Roll V Folder 22
The New York Times Roll IV Book 3 Roll V Folder 25
The New York Tribune Roll V Folder 25
The New York World Roll IV Book 3
Nobel Peace Prize Roll V Folder 25
Noel, John V. Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
The North American Review Roll V Book 23, Folder 25
North Venezuelan Petroleum Company Roll V Folder 24
Norton, Mrs. T. H. Roll IV Book 3
Noyes, Theodore R. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5 Roll V Folder 22
Noyes, Thomas C. Roll IV Book 3, Book 5
Oakland Tribune Roll V Folder 25
Ochs, Adolph Roll IV Book 5
O'Connell, John J. Roll IV Book 5 Roll V Folder 19
Odell, H. Allen Roll III Book 1 Roll IV Book 3, Book 5 Roll V Book 21, Folder 23
Ohio Republican Association Roll IV Book 5
Ohl, Joseph K. Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5
Ojeda, Emilio Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3
O'Laughlin, John C. Roll IV Book 5 Roll V Book 21, Folder 23
Olcott, R. Morgan Roll III Book 1, Book 2 Roll IV Book 3, Book 4, Book 5 Roll V Book 19, Folder 20
Oldham, Wylie E. Roll III Book 1
Open Door Policy Roll V Folder 22
O'Reilly, Robert M. Roll IV Book 3
Orinoco Steamship and Trading Company Roll V Folder 19